affect3dstore.com 2019-03-31

# Affect3D Store - Privacy Policy

Last updated August 2018

This privacy policy sets out how Affect3D Store uses and protects any information that you give Affect3D Store when you use this website. Affect3D Store is committed to ensuring that your privacy is protected. Should we ask you to provide certain information by which you can be identified when using this website, then you can be assured that it will only be used in accordance with this privacy statement. Affect3D Store may change this policy from time to time by updating this page. You should check this page from time to time to ensure that you are happy with any changes. If you have any questions about this privacy policy, the practices of the site, or your dealings with this site, you may contact us by email at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## What data we collect

### Personal identification information 

We may collect personal identification information from Users in a variety of ways, including, but not limited to, when Users visit our site, register on the site, place an order, subscribe to the newsletter, and in connection with other activities, services, features or resources we make available on our Site. Users may be asked for, as appropriate, name, email address, mailing address, and/or phone number. Users may, however, visit our site anonymously. We will collect personal identification information from users only if they voluntarily submit such information to us. Users can always refuse to supply personal identification information, except that it may prevent them from engaging in certain site-related activities. No credit card information is collected or stored by Affect3D Store unless explicitly requested by the User.

### Non-personal identification information 

We may collect non-personal identification information about Users whenever they interact with our Site. Non-personal identification information may include the browser name, the type of computer and technical information about Users means of connection to our Site, such as the operating system, the Internet service providers utilized, country, and other similar information.

## Web browser cookies

Our Site may use "cookies" to enhance User experience. A cookie is a small file which asks permission to be placed on your computer's hard drive. User's web browser places cookies on their hard drive for record-keeping purposes and sometimes to track information about them. User may choose to set their web browser to refuse cookies, or to alert you when cookies are being sent. If they do so, note that some parts of the Site may not function properly. Once you accept a cookie, the file is added and the cookie can perform a number of tasks, such as analyse web traffic, or customizing the browsing experience. Cookies allow web applications to respond to you as an individual. The web application can tailor its operations to your needs, likes and dislikes by gathering and remembering information about your preferences.

We primarily use traffic log cookies to identify which pages are being used. This helps us analyse data about web page traffic and improve our website in order to tailor it to customer needs. We only use this information for statistical analysis purposes and then the data is removed from the system. 

Overall, cookies help us provide you with a better website, by enabling us to monitor which pages you find useful and which you do not. A cookie in no way gives us access to your computer or any information about you, other than the data you choose to share with us. You can choose to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. This may prevent you from taking full advantage of the website. 

For more information on the cookies we use see the cookies we use section.

## What we do with the information we gather

Affect3D primarily collects and uses Users personal information for the following purposes: 

  * Payment processing and internal record keeping - We may use the information Users provide about themselves when placing an order only to provide service to that order. We do not share this information with outside parties except to the extent necessary to provide the service. Payment details such as credit card numbers are encrypted and transmitted to our payment processor via SSL, and are not visible to our staff.
  * Periodic emails - We may use a provided email address to send User information and updates pertaining to their order. It may also be used to respond to their inquiries, questions, and/or other requests. If User decides to opt-in to our mailing list, they will receive emails that include company news, updates, related product, or service information, etc. If at any time the User would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email or User may contact us via our Site.
  * Monitoring site traffic - We may use the information to improve our products and services.
  * Rewarding our affiliates - Users visiting through affiliate links will have their browsing habits and transactions anonymized and logged for the purposes of rewarding affiliates. 

## Mature Content 

This site contains sexually explicit content, we therefore advise that access is prohibited to persons not of legal age, in most cases this is 18 years of age in some 21 years of age. If you are under the legal age in your country, if visiting adult sites is against the law in your country or if you are offended by sexually explicit material you must leave this site immediately.

## Security

We are committed to ensuring that your information is secure. Sensitive and private data exchanged between the Site, Users, and payment processors happen over a SSL secured communication channel and is encrypted and protect with digital signatures. In order to prevent unauthorised access or disclosure, we have put in place suitable physical, electronic and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online. In the event of a data breach, it is our policy to alert our site users of a data breach as soon as it is detected, unless we are advised by state, national, or international authorities to wait in sharing this information. 

## Links to other websites

Our website may contain links to other websites of interest. However, once you have used these links to leave our site, you should note that we do not have any control over that other website. Therefore, we cannot be responsible for the protection and privacy of any information which you provide whilst visiting such sites and such sites are not governed by this privacy statement. You should exercise caution and look at the privacy statement applicable to the website in question. 

## Controlling your personal information

You may choose to restrict the collection or use of your personal information in the following ways:

  * Whenever you are asked to fill in a form on the website, look for the box that you can click to indicate that you do not want the information to be used by anybody for direct marketing purposes 
  * if you have previously agreed to us using your personal information for direct marketing purposes, you may change your mind at any time by using the unsubscribe information at the bottom of any marketing email, or emailing us at [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

If you have made an account on this site, you can request to receive a copy of the personal data we hold about you under the Data Protection Act 1998. This may include your email address, order history, IP address, emails messages, newsletter records.

You can also request that we erase any personal data we hold about you. This does not include any data we are obliged to keep for administrative, legal, or security purposes. When making such a request, please email us using the email address you are enquiring information for so we can verify you as the owner of the information. Requests can be made to [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

If you believe that any information we are holding on you is incorrect or incomplete, please write to or email us as soon as possible, at the above address. We will promptly correct any information found to be incorrect. 

## Where your data is sent

Due to the global nature of the internet infrastructure the information you provide may be transferred outside both Affect3D’s country of origin, and our third parties’ countries of origin. In some cases this may mean data provided by occupants of the European Economic Area will have their data transmitted outside that area. Some of those areas do not have the same protections in place regarding your data and its use as set out in this policy. By using our site and submitting your information you consent to the transfers of data within and outside of the European Economic Area or your country of origin.

## Changes to this privacy policy

Affect3DStore has the discretion to update this privacy policy at any time. When we do, we will revise the updated date at the bottom of this page. We encourage Users to frequently check this page for any changes to stay informed about how we are helping to protect the personal information we collect. You acknowledge and agree that it is your responsibility to review this privacy policy periodically and become aware of modifications.

## Your acceptance of these terms

By using this Site, you signify your acceptance of this policy. If you do not agree to this policy, please do not use our Site. Your continued use of the Site following the posting of changes to this policy will be deemed your acceptance of those changes.

## Contacting us

If you have any questions about this Privacy Policy, the practices of this site, or your dealings with this site, please contact us at: [[email protected]](https://web.archive.org/cdn-cgi/l/email-protection)

## Cookies we use

COOKIE name | COOKIE Description  
---|---  
CART | The association with your shopping cart.  
CATEGORY_INFO | Stores the category info on the page, that allows to display pages more quickly.  
COMPARE | The items that you have in the Compare Products list.  
CURRENCY | Your preferred currency  
CUSTOMER | An encrypted version of your customer id with the store.  
CUSTOMER_AUTH | An indicator if you are currently logged into the store.  
CUSTOMER_INFO | An encrypted version of the customer group you belong to.  
CUSTOMER_SEGMENT_IDS | Stores the Customer Segment ID  
EXTERNAL_NO_CACHE | A flag, which indicates whether caching is disabled or not.  
FRONTEND | You sesssion ID on the server.  
GUEST-VIEW | Allows guests to edit their orders.  
LAST_CATEGORY | The last category you visited.  
LAST_PRODUCT | The most recent product you have viewed.  
NEWMESSAGE | Indicates whether a new message has been received.  
NO_CACHE | Indicates whether it is allowed to use cache.  
PERSISTENT_SHOPPING_CART | A link to information about your cart and viewing history if you have asked the site.  
POLL | The ID of any polls you have recently voted in.  
POLLN | Information on what polls you have voted on.  
RECENTLYCOMPARED | The items that you have recently compared.   
STF | Information on products you have emailed to friends.  
STORE | The store view or language you have selected.  
USER_ALLOWED_SAVE_COOKIE | Indicates whether a customer allowed to use cookies.  
VIEWED_PRODUCT_IDS | The products that you have recently viewed.  
WISHLIST | An encrypted list of products added to your Wishlist.  
WISHLIST_CNT | The number of items in your Wishlist.  
  
### Third party cookies

We use a number of Google services on this site to both improve the browsing experience for site users and to provide statistical data for our web development team. Google Analytics, and Google Tag Manager are the primary services we use. These cookies will generally last up to two years. Most of the data collected by these cookies is anonymized, meaning no personally identifying information is collected by our website or transmitted to Google for processing. Some cookies do transmit identifying data, however, such as when the user activates a service (such as clicking on an embedded YouTube video). For information on Google’s privacy policies, you may visit http://www.google.com/privacy.html.

Users visiting our website through an affiliate link will have a cookie installed in their browser by TooMuchMedia.com. This cookie transmits IP addresses and some browser agent data to TooMuchMedia. This cookie lasts for 90 days. We use this information to reward affiliates who have promoted our content on their own websites.
